Guide to the Stanford University Student Online Publications Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University student online publications collection
2012-2013
SC1099
Stanford University
3298 megabyte(s) (41565 files in 30550 directories)
The materials consist of Stanford University student publication websites captured by University Archives staff.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Accruals
Web sites selected for inclusion in the collection are scheduled for capture on a recurring basis, usually at least once per year.
Physical Characteristics / Technical Requirements
The websites were captured using HTTrack, a free offline browser utility. HTTrack downloads a website from the Internet to a local directory, building recursively all directories, getting HTML, images, and other files from the server to your computer. HTTrack arranges the original site's relative link-structure allowing you to open a page of the mirrored website in your browser and browse the site from link to link.
Scope and Content
The materials consist of Stanford University student publication websites captured by University Archives staff.
Arrangement note
Web sites are listed alphabetically by publication title.
Access Terms
College students--California--Stanford.; Stanford University--Students.; Student publications.
Collection Contents
- Avicenna – The Stanford Journal on Muslim Affairs [http://stanford.edu/group/avicenna/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 27, avicenna20120227; 42.9 megabyte(s) (71 files in 20 directories)
- The Claw [http://theclawmagazine.com/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 23, claw20120223; 88 megabyte(s) (1495 files in 1374 directories)
- Leland Quarterly [http://lelandquarterly.com/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 27, lelandq20120227; 239 megabyte(s) (1,953 files in 1,769 directories)
- SAUTI: Stanford Journal of African Studies [http://www.stanford.edu/group/sauti/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 27, sauti20120227; 44.4 megabyte(s) (22 files in 9 directories)
- Six Degrees: A Stanford Journal of Human Rights [http://stanfordsixdegrees.wordpress.com/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 27, sixdegrees20120227; 2.6 megabyte(s) (109 files in 80 directories)
- The Stanford Chaparral [http://www.stanfordchaparral.com/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 23, chaparral20120223; 156 megabyte(s) (1246 files in 51 directories)
- The Stanford Flipside [http://stanfordflipside.com/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 23, flipside20120223; 945 megabyte(s) (13,554 files in 8,743 directories)
  - 2012 Jun 19, flipside20120619; 776 megabyte(s) 14,369 files in 9,472 directories
- Stanford Journal of East Asian Affairs [http://sjeaa.stanford.edu/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 27, sjeaa20120227; 35.9 megabyte(s) (113 files in 13 directories)
- Stanford Journal of International Relations [http://www.stanford.edu/group/sjir/], 2012
  - 2012 Feb 27, sjir20120227; 76.5 megabyte(s)
- Stanford Journal of Public Health [http://www.stanford.edu/group/sjph/cgi-bin/sjphsite/]
  - 2013 Mar 29, sjph20130329
- The Stanford Progressive [http://progressive.stanford.edu/], 2012
  - 2012 Jul 16, progressive20120716; 79.4 megabyte(s) (485 files in 57 directories)
- The Stanford Review [http://stanfordreview.org/], 2012
  - 2012 Jul 17, review20120717; 285 megabyte(s) (7,938 files in 8,931 directories)
- Stanford Service in Global Health [http://www.stanford.edu/group/ssgh/], 2012
  - 2012 Jul 16, ssgh20120716; 51 megabyte(s) (51 files in 4 directories)
- Vox Clara [http://www.voxstanford.org/], 2012
  - 2012 Jul 16, voxclara20120716; 117 megabyte(s) (17 files in 4 directories)